hey guys welcome back to my channel so
uh today i'm shooting this video because
lot of a lot of you guys had questions
on applying dubai visa so this is the
latest update in july 2022 well you've
been asking uh this from you know maybe
a month or two so there is a latest
update when applying for dubai visa
through make my trip so a lot of few
people as you can see on the screen now
there is an introduction um uh a new
introduction of a medical insurance uh
for applying
uh dubai visit visa through make my trip
and as you can see i'm getting a lot of
pings asking for the same to instagram
through youtube comments so i thought of
making a video so it's easier i'll try
to tag this uh video in my main video
that about my dubai visa which whichever
i've explained so the update is very
very simple uh every uh now whenever you
are playing dubai visa whether it is
through make my trip or whether it is
through an agency whether it is through
thomas cook or any other agency or
through dubai embassy itself a medical
insurance is mandatory so how is this
different from a normal insurance or
travel insurance it is not different at
all so you can just go to google you can
just type medical insurance for dubai
visa and it's going to show up a lot of
links a lot of companies like tata aeg
htfc ergo um icc lombard
axa insurance there's a lot of insurance
companies that are already providing
this so my recommendation is either icha
lombard or tata aig a few of my friends
have traveled to dubai in the last 15
days and they have applied this medical
insurance through tata aig i don't know
the exact price it depends on number of
days you travel and uh from where are
you going etc uh so it'll roughly come
around 500 to 800 rupees if you take the
10 000 or the 25 000
version so i'll leave those links in the
description below so you can just click
on it and you can just go and apply it
so what happens uh when you uh when you
apply this medical insurance is whenever
make my trip uh contacts the embassy
with all your details so when i say all
your details all your details as in
whether it is your passport front and
back copy or the passport size photo
they are also going to apply with the
medical insurance pdf and the number
that you upload when applying for a make
my trip uh visit to buy visit visa so
they need this details uh to help you
guys with this particular
visa they need the medical insurance
which is a mandatory now and whether you
go on like i said whether you go on a
package or whether it goes through
thomas coke or whether you go alone you
definitely need a visa and you have to
take medical insurance that is mandatory
so a lot of you guys ask me whether this
medical insurance is just for mmt and
not for uh when you're applying uh
individually through other agency this
is completely false information through
whichever agency you are applying your
dubai visit visa you definitely need a
medical insurance that is uh that is a
proper medical insurance not a fake one
so you can go and apply uh in tata aeg
that i recommend uh you can also go to
ics lombard or htc go or axa or go to um
policy bazaar or bank bazaar and compare
all these insurances but i'll leave the
links to at least start ig and icsa
lombard in the description below you can
click that it'll redirect you to that
website and you can purchase your
insurance and you can follow the same
video whichever uploaded in the
beginning the process remains same
there's no need to make another video
but the only addition is about this mmt
update i'm sure you guys got to know now
so if you have any questions even now
feel free to reach out to me on
instagram for
immediate response i've linked my
instagram instagram id in the comment
section below or if you have any
questions if you if you want to know
about anything in dubai i've also made a
dedicated dubai playlist uh you can go
and check out all my dubai videos about
burj khalifa desert safari uh dubai full
tour plan etc any information on dubai
uh most importantly vat refund as well
so if you want any information on all of
these things uh please feel free to
contact me on instagram for immediate
response or if you want to comment in
the comment section i have replied to
all the comments as you can see in the
pre my previous videos by taking my time
off for replying to these comments so i
hope you
found this video helpful please share it
with your friends and family or whoever
looking it looking to go to dubai so um
i'll catch you in my next video and
thank you so much